tutoruniverse.com 2013-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Tutor Universe

**We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised terms at: _ ___**[**_http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy) **.  All changes are effective immediately when we post them.  We will notify you through the Tutor Universe Messaging and/or via email of any material changes to this Privacy Policy.  You are required to agree to the changes to the Privacy Policy prior to further use of the Tutor Universe website.  If you do not indicate your agreement, your access to the website features and functions may be limited or terminated. **

**_Tutor Universe, Inc._** **(“Tutor Universe,”** **"Company,"** or **"We"** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [**_http://www.tutoruniverse.com_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/) (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect: 

  * On this Website and all related sites, applications, services, and tools where this policy is referenced; 
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website; and
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy. 

It does not apply to information collected by: 

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or 
  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By agreeing to the Terms of Use, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time-to-time, review the last revisedPrivacy Policy at _:_[ ** _http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy).  Material changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website and will be sent to you through the Tutor Universe Messaging and/or via email.  You will be required to agree to the changes to the Privacy Policy prior to further use of the Website.   

**Information Sharing and Registration with Social Media Websites**

We offer sign-on services that allow you to use third party login credentials to access the Tutor Universe website. We also offer services that allow you to share information with third party social media websites such as Facebook, Google Plus, Twitter, and others.

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by such third party websites. The personal information we have access to varies by website and is controlled by your privacy settings on that website and your consent.  By associating an account managed by a third party with your Tutor Universe account and authorizing Tutor Universe to have access to this information, you agree that Tutor Universe may collect, use and store information from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or member name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at: **_Attn: Chief Privacy Officer, legal@tutoruniverse.com_**. 

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information: 

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number ("personal information");
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as education, expertise, or work experience; and/or
  * About your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details. 

We collect this information: 

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us;
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies; and
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners or vendors.

**Information You Provide to Us.**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website; 
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us;
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes;
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website;
  * Your search queries on the Website; and
  * Your social network website that you allow us to access. 

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “Member Contributions”). Your Member Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages/you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, although we use commercially reasonable efforts to comply with your selection of privacy level for your Member Contribution, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your Member Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your Member Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. 

**_Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies_**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website; and
  * Information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not identify any individual other than to recognize your equipment when you log on.  It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns; 
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests;
  * Speed up your searches; and
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website; 
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see [**Settings Manager for Adobe Flash Player**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html) **;** and
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our the Website and e-mails sent by us may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you;
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * To provide you with notices about your account and subscriptions, including expiration and renewal notices;
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it;
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website;
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data, the registration form or adjust your member preferences in your account profile. 

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates;
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them which purposes have been fully disclosed herein;
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Tutor Universe's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Tutor Universe about our Website users is among the assets transferred. A transfer will include the Privacy obligations described herein;
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to and not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them which purposes have been fully disclosed herein;
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an e-mail address to use the "e-mail a friend" feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and your e-mail address to the recipients;
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; and
  * With your consent; and

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
  * To enforce or apply our _Terms of Use -_ [**_http://www.tutoruniverse.com/terms-of-use_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/terms-of-use) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; and
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Tutor Universe, our members or others.  This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  *  

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.** If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your member preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to: Attn: OPT OUT, support@tutoruniverse.com; 
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your e-mail address/contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your member preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to: Attn: OPT OUT, support@tutoruniverse.com; If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions; and 
  * **Targeted Advertising.** If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to: Attn: OPT OUT, support@tutoruniverse.com;

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. 

You may also send us an e-mail at: Attn: Update Profile Information, support@tutoruniverse.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete all of your personal information except by also deleting your member account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your Member Contributions from the Website, copies of your Member Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including Member Contributions, is governed by our _Terms of Use -_ [**_http://www.tutoruniverse.com/terms-of-use_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/terms-of-use).

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send email to:

**Attn: Information Regarding Disclosure of Personal Information, support@tutoruniverse.com**

or 

**write us at: Customer Service, Tutor Universe, Inc., 322 N. Clinton St., Suite 204, Iowa City, 52245, Attn: Information Regarding Disclosure of Personal Information.**

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and financial accounts and credit card information will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you or where you have chosen a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.  The Terms of Use require that you not share this password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. Any user of the Website may view the information you share in public areas.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.  

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised terms on this site - ** _ ___**[**_http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy_**](http://www.tutoruniverse.com/privacy-policy).  All changes are effective immediately when we post them. We will notify you through the Tutor Universe Messaging and/or via email of any material changes to this Privacy Policy.  You will be requested to agree to the Terms of Use after a material change to this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use or the Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy.  If you do not indicate your agreement, your access to the Website features and functions may be limited or terminated.  You are expected to check this page from time to time/frequently/each time you access this Website so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. 

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:  
**_Attn: Chief Privacy Officer, legal@tutoruniverse.com_**  
Or call 319-855-1595
